Guide to the Football Game Film Collection, 1934-2007 UA.13.01.0004
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Football Game Films
  - Navy, 1964 November 14
    - Duke vs. Navy: First Quarter, 1964 November 14; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 70, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0605)
    - Duke vs. Navy: Second Quarter, 1964 November 14; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 70, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0606)
    - Duke vs. Navy: Third Quarter, 1964 November 14; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 70, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0607)
    - Duke vs. Navy: Fourth Quarter, 1964 November 14; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 70, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0608)
  - North Carolina, 1964 November 21
    Duke loss, score: 15-21
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Second Quarter, 1964 November 21; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 69, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0609)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Third Quarter, 1964 November 21; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 69, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0610)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Fourth Quarter, 1964 November 21; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 69, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0611)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Defense 1, 1964 November 21; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 69, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0612)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Defense 2, 1964 November 21; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 69, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0613)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Offense 2, 1964 November 21; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 69, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0614)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Offense 1, 1964 November 21; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 69, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0615)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Defense, Offense, Game, 1964 November 21; DVD
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Defense, 1964 November 21; VHS
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Offense, 1964 November 21; VHS
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: All, 1964 November 21; VHS
  - Tulane, 1964 November 28
    Duke loss, score: 9-17
    - Duke vs. Tulane: First Half Offense, 1964 November 28; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 71, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0616)
    - Duke vs. Tulane: Second Half Offense, 1964 November 28; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 71, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0617)
    - Duke vs. Tulane: First Half Defense, 1964 November 28; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 71, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0618)
    - Duke vs. Tulane: Second Half Defense, 1964 November 28; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 71, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0619)
    - Duke vs. Tulane: First Half Offense, 1964 November 28; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 71, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0620)
    - Duke vs. Tulane: Unidentified game coverage, 1964 November 28; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 71, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0621)
  - Virginia, 1965 September 18
    - Duke vs. Virginia: 1 of 3 regular, 1965 September 18; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 74, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0622)
    - Duke vs. Virginia: 2 of 3 regular, 1965 September 18; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 74, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0623)
    - Duke vs. Virginia: 3 of 3 regular, 1965 September 18; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 74, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0624)
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Offense 1, 1965 September 18; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 74, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0625)
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Offense 2, 1965 September 18; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 74, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0626)
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Defense 1, 1965 September 18; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 75, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0627)
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Defense 2, 1965 September 18; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 75, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0628)
  - South Carolina, 1965 September 25
    Duke win, score: 20-15
    - Duke vs. South Carolina: Offense 1, 1965 September 25; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 73, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0629)
    - Duke vs. South Carolina: Offense 2, 1965 September 25; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 73, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0630)
    - Duke vs. South Carolina: Defense 1, 1965 September 25; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 73, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0631)
    - Duke vs. South Carolina: Defense 2, 1965 September 25; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 73, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0632)
  - Rice, 1965 October 02
    Duke win, score: 41-21
    - Duke vs. Rice: First Quarter, 1965 October 02; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 75, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0633)
    - Duke vs. Rice: Second Quarter, 1965 October 02; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 75, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0634)
    - Duke vs. Rice: Third Quarter, 1965 October 02; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 75, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0635)
    - Duke vs. Rice: Fourth Quarter, 1965 October 02; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 75, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0636)
    - Duke vs. Rice: Offense 1, 1965 October 02; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 75, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0637)
    - Duke vs. Rice: Offense 2, 1965 October 02; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 75, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0638)
    - Duke vs. Rice: Defense 1, 1965 October 02; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 75, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0639)
    - Duke vs. Rice: Defense 2, 1965 October 02; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 75, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0640)
    - Duke vs. Rice: Defense 1, 1965 October 02; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 105, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0641)
  - Pittsburgh, 1965 October 09
    Duke win, score: 21-13
    - Duke vs. Pittsburgh: First Quarter, 1965 October 09; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 76, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0642)
    - Duke vs. Pittsburgh: Second Quarter, 1965 October 09; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 76, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0643)
    - Duke vs. Pittsburgh: Third Quarter, 1965 October 09; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 76, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0644)
    - Duke vs. Pittsburgh: Fourth Quarter, 1965 October 09; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 76, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0645)
    - Duke vs. Pittsburgh: 1 Offense regular, 1965 October 09; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 75, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0646)
    - Duke vs. Pittsburgh: 2 Offense regular, 1965 October 09; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 75, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0647)
    - Duke vs. Pittsburgh: Defense 1 regular, 1965 October 09; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 76, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0648)
    - Duke vs. Pittsburgh: 2 Defense regular, 1965 October 09; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 76, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0649)
    - Duke vs. Pittsburgh: 1 Offense wide, 1965 October 09; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 76, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0650)
    - Duke vs. Pittsburgh: 2 Offense wide, 1965 October 09; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 76, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0651)
    - Duke vs. Pittsburgh: Defense 1 wide, 1965 October 09; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 76, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0652)
    - Duke vs. Pittsburgh: 2 Defense wide, 1965 October 09; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 76, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0653)
  - Clemson, 1965 October 16
    Duke loss, score: 2-3
    - Duke vs. Clemson: 1 Offense regular, 1965 October 16; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 76, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0654)
    - Duke vs. Clemson: 2 Offense regular, 1965 October 16; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 76, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0655)
    - Duke vs. Clemson: Defense 1 regular, 1965 October 16; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 76, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0656)
    - Duke vs. Clemson: 2 Defense regular, 1965 October 16; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 76, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0657)
    - Duke vs. Clemson: 1 Offense wide, 1965 October 16; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 76, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0658)
    - Duke vs. Clemson: 2 Offense wide, 1965 October 16; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 76, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0659)
    - Duke vs. Clemson: Defense 1 wide, 1965 October 16; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 76, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0660)
    - Duke vs. Clemson: 2 Defense wide, 1965 October 16; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 76, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0661)
  - Illinois, 1965 October 23
    - Duke vs. Illinois: First Quarter regular, 1965 October 23; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 72, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0662)
    - Duke vs. Illinois: Second Quarter regular, 1965 October 23; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 72, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0663)
    - Duke vs. Illinois: Third Quarter regular, 1965 October 23; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 72, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0664)
    - Duke vs. Illinois: Fourth Quarter regular, 1965 October 23; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 72, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0665)
    - Duke vs. Illinois: First Quarter wide, 1965 October 23; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 72, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0666)
    - Duke vs. Illinois: Second Quarter wide, 1965 October 23; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 73, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0667)
    - Duke vs. Illinois: Third Quarter wide, 1965 October 23; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 73, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0668)
    - Duke vs. Illinois: Fourth Quarter wide, 1965 October 23; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 73, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0669)
    - Duke vs. Illinois: Offense 1, 1965 October 23; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 73, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0670)
    - Duke vs. Illinois: Offense 2, 1965 October 23; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 73, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0671)
    - Duke vs. Illinois: Defense 1, 1965 October 23; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 73, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0672)
    - Duke vs. Illinois: Defense 2, 1965 October 23; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 73, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0673)
  - Georgia Tech, 1965 October 30
    Duke loss, score: 23-35
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: First Quarter, 1965 October 30; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 74, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0674)
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: Second Quarter, 1965 October 30; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 74, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0675)
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: Third Quarter, 1965 October 30; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 74, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0676)
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: Fourth Quarter, 1965 October 30; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 74, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0677)
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: Offense 1, 1965 October 30; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 73, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0678)
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: Offense 2, 1965 October 30; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 74, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0679)
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: Defense 1, 1965 October 30; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 74, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0680)
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: Defense 2, 1965 October 30; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 74, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0681)
  - NC State, 1965 November 06
    - Duke vs. NC State: First Quarter, 1965 November 06; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 74, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0682)
    - Duke vs. NC State: Second Quarter, 1965 November 06; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 74, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0683)
    - Duke vs. NC State: Third Quarter, 1965 November 06; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 74, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0684)
    - Duke vs. NC State: Fourth Quarter, 1965 November 06; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 74, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0685)
    - Duke vs. NC State: Offense 1, 1965 November 06; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 74, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0686)
    - Duke vs. NC State: Offense 2, 1965 November 06; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 74, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0687)
    - Duke vs. NC State: Defense 1, 1965 November 06; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 74, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0688)
    - Duke vs. NC State: Defense 2, 1965 November 06; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 74, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0689)
  - Wake Forest, 1965 November 13
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: First Quarter, 1965 November 13; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 73, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0690)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Second Quarter, 1965 November 13; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 73, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0691)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Third Quarter, 1965 November 13; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 73, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0692)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Fourth Quarter, 1965 November 13; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 73, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0693)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Offense 1, 1965 November 13; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 73, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0694)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Offense 2, 1965 November 13; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 73, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0695)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Defense 1, 1965 November 13; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 73, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0696)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Defense 2, 1965 November 13; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 73, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0697)
  - North Carolina, 1965 November 20
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: First Quarter regular, 1965 November 20; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 75, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0698)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Second Quarter regular, 1965 November 20; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 75, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0699)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Third Quarter regular, 1965 November 20; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 75, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0700)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Fourth Quarter regular, 1965 November 20; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 75, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0701)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: First Quarter wide, 1965 November 20; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 75, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0702)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Second Quarter wide, 1965 November 20; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 75, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0703)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Third Quarter wide, 1965 November 20; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 75, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0704)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Fourth Quarter wide, 1965 November 20; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 75, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0705)
  - West Virginia, 1966 September 17
    Duke win, score: 34-15
    - Duke vs. West Virginia: 1 of 3 black and white, 1966 September 17; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 79, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0706)
    - Duke vs. West Virginia: 2 of 3 black and white, 1966 September 17; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 79, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0707)
    - Duke vs. West Virginia: 3 of 3 black and white, 1966 September 17; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 79, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0708)
    - Duke vs. West Virginia: 1 Offense color, 1966 September 17; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 79, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0709)
    - Duke vs. West Virginia: 2 Offense color, 1966 September 17; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 79, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0710)
    - Duke vs. West Virginia: Defense color, 1966 September 17; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 79, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0711)
    - Duke vs. West Virginia: Kick color, 1966 September 17; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 79, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0712)
  - Pitt, 1966 September 24
    - Duke vs. Pitt: 1 of 3 black and white, 1966 September 24; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 79, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0713)
    - Duke vs. Pitt: 2 of 3 black and white, 1966 September 24; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 79, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0714)
    - Duke vs. Pitt: 3 of 3 black and white, 1966 September 24; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 79, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0715)
    - Duke vs. Pitt: Offense 1, 1966 September 24; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 79, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0716)
    - Duke vs. Pitt: Offense 2, 1966 September 24; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 79, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0717)
    - Duke vs. Pitt: Defense, 1966 September 24; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 79, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0718)
    - Duke vs. Pitt: Kick, 1966 September 24; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 79, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0719)
  - Virginia, 1966 October 01
    Duke win, score: 27-8
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Unidentified game coverage, 1966 October 01; 16mm film: 12" reel (Box 115, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0720)
    - Duke vs. Virginia: First Quarter, 1966 October 01; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 79, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0721)
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Second Quarter, 1966 October 01; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 79, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0722)
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Third Quarter, 1966 October 01; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 79, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0723)
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Fourth Quarter, 1966 October 01; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 79, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0724)
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Kick, 1966 October 01; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 80, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0725)
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Offense 1, 1966 October 01; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 80, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0726)
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Offense 2, 1966 October 01; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 80, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0727)
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Defense, 1966 October 01; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 80, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0728)
  - Maryland, 1966 October 08
    Duke loss, score: 19-21
    - Duke vs. Maryland: 1 of 3 black and white, 1966 October 08; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 77, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0729)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: 2 of 3 black and white, 1966 October 08; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 77, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0730)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: 3 of 3 black and white, 1966 October 08; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 77, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0731)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Kick black and white, 1966 October 08; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 77, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0732)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Offense, 1966 October 08; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 76, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0733)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Defense, 1966 October 08; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 76, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0734)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: color, 1966 October 08; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 77, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0735)
  - Clemson, 1966 October 15
    Duke loss, score: 6-9
    - Duke vs. Clemson: First Quarter, 1966 October 15; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 78, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0736)
    - Duke vs. Clemson: Second Quarter, 1966 October 15; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 78, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0737)
    - Duke vs. Clemson: Third Quarter, 1966 October 15; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 78, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0738)
    - Duke vs. Clemson: Fourth Quarter, 1966 October 15; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 78, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0739)
    - Duke vs. Clemson: Kick, 1966 October 15; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 78, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0740)
    - Duke vs. Clemson: game film coverage: Offenseense, 1966 October 15; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 78, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0741)
    - Duke vs. Clemson: Defense 1, 1966 October 15; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 78, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0742)
    - Duke vs. Clemson: Defense 2, 1966 October 15; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 78, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0743)
  - NC State, 1966 October 22
    Duke loss, score: 7-33
    - Duke vs. NC State: First Quarter, 1966 October 22; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 84, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0744)
    - Duke vs. NC State: Second Quarter, 1966 October 22; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 84, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0745)
    - Duke vs. NC State: Third Quarter, 1966 October 22; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 84, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0746)
    - Duke vs. NC State: Fourth Quarter, 1966 October 22; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 84, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0747)
    - Duke vs. NC State: Offense 1, 1966 October 22; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 84, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0748)
    - Duke vs. NC State: Offense 2, 1966 October 22; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 84, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0749)
    - Duke vs. NC State: Defense 1, 1966 October 22; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 84, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0750)
    - Duke vs. NC State: Defense 2, 1966 October 22; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 84, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0751)
    - Duke vs. NC State: Kick, 1966 October 22; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 84, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0752)
  - Georgia Tech, 1966 October 29
    Duke loss, score: 7-48
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: First Quarter, 1966 October 29; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 80, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0753)
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: Second Quarter, 1966 October 29; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 80, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0754)
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: Third Quarter, 1966 October 29; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 80, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0755)
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: Fourth Quarter, 1966 October 29; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 80, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0756)
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: Offense 1, 1966 October 29; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 80, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0757)
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: Offense 2, 1966 October 29; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 80, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0758)
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: Defense 1, 1966 October 29; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 80, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0759)
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: Defense 2, 1966 October 29; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 80, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0760)
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: Kick, 1966 October 29; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 80, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0761)
  - Navy, 1966 November 05
    Duke win, score: 9-7
    - Duke vs. Navy: First Quarter color, 1966 November 05; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 77, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0762)
    - Duke vs. Navy: Second Quarter color, 1966 November 05; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 77, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0763)
    - Duke vs. Navy: Third Quarter color, 1966 November 05; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 77, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0764)
    - Duke vs. Navy: Fourth Quarter color, 1966 November 05; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 77, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0765)
    - Duke vs. Navy: 1 of 3 black and white, 1966 November 05; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 78, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0766)
    - Duke vs. Navy: 2 of 3 black and white, 1966 November 05; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 78, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0767)
    - Duke vs. Navy: 3 of 3 black and white, 1966 November 05; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 78, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0768)
  - Notre Dame, 1966 November 12
    Duke loss, score: 0-64
    - Duke vs. Notre Dame: First Quarter black and white, 1966 November 12; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 78, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0769)
    - Duke vs. Notre Dame: Second Quarter black and white, 1966 November 12; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 78, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0770)
    - Duke vs. Notre Dame: Third Quarter black and white, 1966 November 12; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 78, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0771)
    - Duke vs. Notre Dame: Fourth Quarter black and white, 1966 November 12; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 78, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0772)
    - Duke vs. Notre Dame: First Quarter color, 1966 November 12; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 78, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0773)
    - Duke vs. Notre Dame: Second Quarter color, 1966 November 12; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 78, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0774)
    - Duke vs. Notre Dame: Third Quarter color, 1966 November 12; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 78, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0775)
    - Duke vs. Notre Dame: Fourth Quarter color, 1966 November 12; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 78, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0776)
  - North Carolina, 1966 November 19
    Duke win, score: 41-25
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: First Quarter, 1966 November 19; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 77, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0777)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Second Quarter, 1966 November 19; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 77, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0778)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Third Quarter, 1966 November 19; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 77, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0779)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Fourth Quarter, 1966 November 19; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 77, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0780)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: First Quarter, 1966 November 19; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 77, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0781)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Second Quarter, 1966 November 19; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 77, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0782)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Third Quarter, 1966 November 19; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 77, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0783)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Fourth Quarter, 1966 November 19; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 77, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0784)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: UNC Defense, 1966 November 19; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 77, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0785)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Unidentified game coverage, 1966 November 19; DVD
  - Wake Forest, 1967 September 16
    Duke win, score: 31-13
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: 1 of 3, 1967 September 16; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 81, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0786)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: 2 of 3, 1967 September 16; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 81, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0787)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: 3 of 3, 1967 September 16; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 81, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0788)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Offense 1, 1967 September 16; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 81, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0789)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Offense 2, 1967 September 16; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 81, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0790)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Defense 1, 1967 September 16; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 81, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0791)